uid.me 2015-05-26

# 

uID.me is a profile page builder. It is very important to us to keep your privacy when using the Internet, because we want you to feel safe and comfortable.

We collect certain personal information about our users and below are the terms and conditions of obtaining and using this information.

## Information We Collect

uID.me collects two types of information about its users:

  * Information, provided by a user voluntarily. For example, this includes your name and e-mail address, entered when you register an account.
  * Information, obtained through complex tracking and statistical processing of page view dynamics on our websites. This information allows us to improve the provided services and help us understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances uID.me discloses the information about an individual user to third-parties, except as provided by law.

Information about users is collected in the following way:

### Optional information, provided voluntarily

We offer free services that require a user to provide certain personal data voluntarily in the following cases:

#### Registration on the uID.me website in order to use the provided services

When creating an account, a user must provide his/her full name, e-mail address, country of residence, date of birth and gender. No personal information about an individual user is disclosed, except as provided by law. All files, uploaded to uID.me, are essentially public and generally available, except for specifically indicated cases of secure access.

#### Polls

We may conduct interactive polls among users, so that the users could share their opinion with each other, and to determine audience’s opinions on various issues. Poll results are summarized and cannot be associated with a certain user. uID.me can apply "marking" tools to poll participants to prevent multiple voting on the same question. Such marker is in no way bound to a certain user.

#### Surveys

uID.me may ocassionally conduct surveys among users in order to provide better services and materials. We may share demographic summary of the surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners, but we never share information about a certain user with third parties.

### Recording Visits

uID.me counts user traffic on all pages. However, we in no way associate this information with the data of certain users. uID.me analyzes overall statistics on user’s page, country, browser and operating system by reading this information from the browser address bar (information contained in every user’s browser).

uID.me tracks search phrases, entered into the search forms on the website, but this information is never associated with a certain user. We analyze user traffic to know what is most popular and vice versa. We do not track what a certain user reads, and only count the total number of views of each page. This helps us provide better services.

### Cookies

We may add a special file called "cookie" to the browser files on your computer. It does not contain your personal information but allows us to associate your usage of the website with the information that you provided voluntarily. The cookies cannot read data from your hard disk or files, created by other websites. uID.me also uses cookies to count traffic (as described above).

You can reject the cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies, you will get a notification about each such event. You are not required to enable cookies to use our website. But cookies are required to create and edit a personal page.

## Usage of Information

uID.me uses all information, provided by users voluntarily, to add new and improve the existing services that would be most consistent with users’ interests and needs.

We analyze user traffic to know what is most popular and vice versa. We do not track what a certain user reads, and only count the total number of views of each page. This helps us provide better services. We track search phrases, entered by users into the search forms, to record interests of our users.

uID.me creates summary reports on user demographics and traffic. It helps our advertisers to offer more suitable services. No personal information about an individual user is disclosed, except as provided by law.

## Disclosure of Information

uID.me uses the types of information, described above, to adapt the services and content to your needs and to better understand the audience’s demographics. This is necessary to ensure that our services continue to remain free. No personal information about an individual user is disclosed, except as provided by law.

## Security

Our Security and Privacy Policy is regularly reviewed and improved, and only authorized individuals have access to the information, provided by users.

## Spyware / Adware

We have strict policy against spyware and adware, applicable to all uID.me users without exception. Any display of such activity by uID.me users leads to immediate deletion of their accounts without notice.

## Your Consent

By using this website you agree to the terms of collection and usage of the information described above. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will make changes to this page, so that you are always aware what information is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances it is disclosed.
